# Hunter C. Beezley

# Sr. Technical Support Engineer

Seasoned Technical Support Engineer with over 10 years of experience helping customers maintain smooth operations and a magical user experience across a variety of technical products. Currently leading support as a subject matter expert in IAM, SSO, API's, Usage and Security for enterprise customers in data observability technologies.

# **Work History**

### 2022-05 -Current

# Sr. Technical Support Engineer

New Relic, Portland, OR

- Leading Accounts-Security team; one of the highest functioning and successful teams in Global Technical Support.
- Advising team of 9 across 3 timezones on technical challenges in support cases and mentoring 1:1 to advance individual skillsets.
- Increasing efficiency and accuracy by creating and updating technical support processes and wiki documentation.
- Working with leaders and stakeholders to creatively solve significant challenges in support while maintaining affective customer support experiences.

### 2021-09 -2022-05

# **Technical Support Engineer**

New Relic, Portland, OR.

# 2019-01 -

# **Associate Technical Support Engineer**

2021-09 New Relic, Portland, OR

# 2019-01 -2019-07

# Cellular QA Engineer

Apple, Inc., Sunnyvale, CA.

- Operated as QA Engineer for Apple Watch and iPhone cellular audio quality within Wireless Technology and Ecosystems team
- Quickly and independently became proficient in discovering, filing and tracking bugs, as well as

### Contact

#### **Phone**

914.319.2467

#### E-mail

hunterbeezley@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/hunterbeezley/

### **Skills**

IAM

API's

SAML/SSO

GDPR/CCPA

SQL/GraphQL

Incident Response Management

Software Observability

IOS/macOS/tvOS/watchOS

# **Certifications**

2015-01

Apple Certified Mac Technician (ACMT)

2015-01

Mac Service Certification (MAC-17A)

2022-01

validating their resolution.

- Often assisted in analyzing audio logging layers to better triage bugs.
- Assisted in running automated tests for telephony reliability.

# 2011-01 -2020-01

# Genius

Apple Inc, Portland, OR.

- Recognized for consistent contribution to support's Net Promoter Score.
- Triaged and repaired customer reported software and hardware issues; seeing 20+ customers per day.
- Spearheaded iPhone 5 Quality Program rollout and innovated on workflow procedures to best assist customers.
- Selected by management to operate as six-month store-wide trainer, curating and facilitating training materials for new and existing employees in a variety of different roles.

# 2010-01 -2011-01

# Marketing Team Member

Zipcar, New York, NY.

- Assisted marketing team by facilitating Zipcar sponsored events and drove new membership through creative campaigns
- Collaborated with business and marketing teams for new and fresh opportunities to promote the Zipcar brand.

Apple Service Fundamentals

# **Education**

2013-05 - 2015-05

#### Master of Arts

Union Theological Seminary
- New York, NY
Table Manners and Urban
Renewal: Paul's SocioSpatial Praxis in 1

2009-05 - 2013-05

#### **Bachelor of Arts**

Nyack College - Nyack, NY Cum Laude